iza te o nobashite Reach your hands out,
kaze o kirisaite cut through the wind,
onore no chizu o egaite yuke and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
migi mo hidari mo guchaguchahit *#E We can't even tell left from right
areta umi no you na jidai in this tempest-tossed era
kizukiageta kachikan Sae mo Even the values we've honed
kuzuresarou to shita [PAINT] 1f # : I Don't Like Mondays.  : I Don't Like Mondays. rhuthmZone seem ready to crumble
kuzuresaron to shita seem ready to crumble
rashinban no Sashita Saki ga A Is the compass leading us true.
tadashii no ka douka nante or is it leading us astray?
douse dare ni mo wakaranain da Nobody knows for sure!
fukaku iki o suikonde hitomi tojireba Just breathe deep, close your eyes
ukabi agaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
iza te o nobashite Reach your hands out,
kaze o kirisaite cut through the wind,
kurayami o kettobashite and kick away the darkness!
ima boku wa boku no tame ni I'm doing this for myself,
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou 2 * and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
ronore no iro de egaite yuke Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
ke
REPREC Edited by fedew Subtitles by HatSubs
Castle Interior Perfor- mance Floor
Beam!
There you are!
You're a super-sparkly lizard, I get it already!
111 111
1111 1111 8 UEEN Sparkle!
/.
Tech that lets you fire lasers as much as you want...
Sounds like something Franky would want!
You're dead meat!
You're really sure about this?
Just do it!
Get a load of my Beam!
Swirly Brow ain't gonna break through here on his own!
That's ol' Zoro for ya...
Very well! Prepare the injection, Miyagi!
Hey!
Too deep, too deep!
Oh! I'm sorry!
4 o
You're so heavily bandaged, I don't know where your veins are...
Take them off first!
You're indeed right!
Oh well, let's get on with it anyway...
Are you sure you kno- Yo!
C Onigashimg Skull Doma Right-Brai Tower
38 BF
0.0 HARI
HAR
HAR We'll take care of the rest!
Give Sasaki hell...
Iron Bro!
You guys came back here to back me up?
Yeah!
C O
Hey, Armored Division!
I know you're all having your strings pulled 'cause of some enemy ability,
but it's still an act of treason, and that's a fact!
FR-
BF
Whoa!
:FR-U:
CC BF
BF
38 BF Man, you're one tough pain in the neck, huh?
Was pretty sure I landed some killer hits back there...
You're the one being the hard thorn in my side!
How about you...
...get the hell outta my way?!
10000 BF
BF
Heard all our underlings on the Performance Floor switched sides, too...
I'm headin' there to send everyone that turned against us to hell!
Protect Wano, in my name!
Your might is a valuable asset to me, Yamato!
Is that how a parent ought speak to their child?!
I fought tooth and claw for that Devil Fruit,
and I wasn't about to let you eat it!
I...
was hungry!
I was shocked, too!
I want to set out to sea, and now I cannot swim!
How many times has it been that I've made attempts on your life...
...only to be struck down just as many times!
But it made me stronger, if nothing else!
It was not just those shackles...
...that chained me to this island!
If I do not fight for the sake of my country...
I dare not call myself Oden!
Let's get this party started!
Hmm So that's what they call a Man-Beast Form!
Stupid ass robot! You're just asking to be kicked outta the way!
Trick Mechanism:
Screw Sword!
Bringin' out that nasty sword again?!
I ain't gettin' outta the way for you!
Iron Bro!
Let us help you!
Bring it, Sasaki!
Come on!
got this!
Go help out everyone else, the buncha yas!
Bet you're glad those bums're gone, huh?
Seems like I'm not gonna get any help around here.
Wha?! That thing rotates?!
Do dinos...
CICC
|1
...work that way?!
That's right!
I-It's that technique.!
That ain't good! Get out of here, Iron Bro!
Dumbasses!
Try worrying about yourselves!
Heliceratops!
11 11
RU
BF
- 4
38 111
38 BF
Guyyyys!
What the hell kinda move is that?!
Is he trying to take this to the air?
cC ceec
0000 BF General Left!
BF
Man, is that freakin' cool or what?!
Triceratops...
...are just that kinda dino!
I had no idea...
Is he gonna charge...
...at that speed?!
Yo, dinosaur!
Let's see whatcha got!
General Shield!
1))
Here I...
luuuh?!
Um?
/11
You gotta be kiddin'.
Propellers change the direction of thrust depending on which way they turn.
And he made it rotate the wrong way...
Which explains why he went backwards.
Space to run... Secured!
You're full of it!
Shaddap!
The longer the approach, the stronger my charge!
Countin' on ya, General Shield!
Bulletriceratops!
BF
Crap! My shoulder launcher's gonna blow!
Say goodnight!
You son of a...
0 0
Gotcha!
General...
...Suplex!
0 A
() (0)
Polar Tang The seas near Wand Come back to us, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
If only the Captain were here!
We got all the water out of his lungs, right?
What else can we do?!
Think giving him pills might work?
No, we gotta give him a shot!
His face is turning blue...
Straw Hat!
Wake up!
What do we do?!
#H
Straw Hat! Thank goodness!
Meat!
Huuuuh?!
You're tough all around,
but you've got a gash on your stomach!
This'll put you down for the count!
Franken-Sword:
V-for-Victory Flash!
Nice try, dumbass robot!
Crap! I ain't good with swords!
||
BF
If that's how we're doin' this, then I'll just pull out the biggest tide-turner I got..
Running away? Shame!
Aww, crap...
1 ended up by the Performance Floor!
I can't let this jerk get there!
Bulletriceratops!
BF
BE
BF All set!
Portable Gaon Cannon:
General Cannon!
Who do you think you're messin' with?!
We're terror itself, the Flying Six of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
If I'm goin' down, I'm takin' you with me!
Magnumceratops!
All set!
Franky Radical Beam!
4 =
N The Dog-Dog Fruit,
Mythical Type!
Model: Okuchi-no-Makami. One of the rare Mythical Type fruits!
And a guardian deity of Wano!
Eaten by someone calling themselves "Oden", of all people!
A huge failure on my part.
And that's why I'm telling you...
Protect Wano for me!
You twist the meaning!
1111 111
Orochi had a talent for exploitation.
This country is a weapon factory!
Dominate it by forcing its people to labor!
//
am... Kozuki Oden!
And I shall open Wano's borders.
I shall...
...free its people!
RE
The samurai...
...and this country...
...shall be set loose unto the world!
Blast Breath!
Namuji Glacier Fang!
You won't be opening any borders!
What's this?
Doesn't appear to be your ordinary fog, hm..
* *** * * *
* * * * * * *
V * K *
Robin-san!
** 1111
^ *
"* *
* * * * * O
* * * You've grown up, huh...
Looks like you've become a fine archaeologist, Robin!
**
* * * A *
Mom...
That's right.
Mom's here.
Come to me...
* *
You mustn't, Robin-san!
Illusion Mist...
The fondest memories will lead you to ruin.
What's the matter, Robin?
Come to us!
You see, I know. that this is all an illusion.
It's a pity, too...
This illusion is a mirror..
A mirror that reflects my childish heart...
However...
...while my friends are fighting,
I can't just lose myself in my memories.
Forget about your friends!
/X
K** **
* ** * * * * * *
Saul wouldn't say such things!
History is one of mankind's treasures!
And it will, without a doubt, illuminate the future we'll live in.
Something I'm certain you people wouldn't understand.
Tres Mano:
Freesia!
Why didn't the Illusion Mist..?
Why didn't it work?!
She ran off!
Go! Catch her!
* * * * * * * * * *
I was worried about you, you know!
Oh, Robin-san, you should have told me her mist had no effect on you!
I appreciate you looking out for me, Brook!
For goodness' sake, preying upon others' memories...
Such foul play!
I can't believe Black Maria-sama's Illusion Mist didn't work on either of them!
Oh, my...
Really, now?
She assaulted her own mother...
Truly a wicked woman!
Come no closerrr...!
This castle...
...terifies me!
Noooo!
Brook!
You seem unaffected as well..
Ah, indeed!
That "Illusion Mist" of hers is quite cruel, isn't it?
Amid those mists for fifty years...
How I wished the deaths of my crewmates were but a dream...
D 33
Everybowhoooa!
C Every day, I would see their images dance before me..
...and it would wound me.
We have so much in common, don't we!
Every ordeal we endured was for this very moment!
+* * * * * * * *
Wanyudo Sleeve Swing!
Again with that odd weapon!
Wanyudo Smile Fruit Pug
You won't be running out on me!
**
Illusions don't affect you, you say?
* * ** *+ ** And yet, you are still caught in a dream!
A dream where you can defeat Kaido-sama!
Spider Net!
My hero!
The floor's a sea of flame!
If you don't stop now, the fire will spread throughout the castle!
You're concerned about us?
Oh, thank you...
Why not surrender to us, then... Nico Robin!
Robin-san, mind keeping hold of me for a bit?
If that is a living weapon...
Soul:
Cold Soul!
That's coooold!
Wanyudo!
Being hot, or far too hot, is prohibited!
Damn you!
mr
* * *
Soul Parade:
Iceburn!
You don't know when to give in, do you...
Nico Robin!
You see it, do you not?
No matter how you look at it, your friend has betrayed you!
Black Leg called for you, before my very eyes... Knowing full well that I was seeking you out!
That is to say.
The fact you are highly sought after by the world's great movers...
...makes you a liability to your crewmates!
That is why he called for you without a second thought!
Help me, Robin-chan!
Black-Leg is the laughingstock of all Onigashima!
He holds the second highest bounty among your crew, no?
What a display of your crew's true strength!
Oh, that Sanji-san...
I nearly split a seam laughing!
May I leave her to you?
That's what I had in mind. Thank you!
Then I shall tend to the other beasts that roam the night!
Though I'm afraid of ghosts!
Do you feel hurt by him?
No.
He's a kind person.
And there's no need for you to understand..
...why he asked for my help!
He is a man worthy of being the wings...
...of the Pirate King.
Gigante Fleurs!
Angry, are we?
I had no idea you could grow so large!
It must take a toll on you, though...
No need to worry.
This was over before it even began!
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
You...!
Don't even try!
Take this!
Do not expect to entrap me without a fight!
So your true body takes the punishment, eh?
Good thing, then, that my target is so massive!
Quite the number of arms!
Also just as large!
Oh, you noticed?
The poison barbs on the ends of my legs!
Marianette!
* *
DEA
RE
Tokage Port Land of Wano Meat! I want more meat!
C'mon, haul up more!
He's already eaten all the provisions aboard the boat!
I don't think we can find meat around here.
Luffy!
AN
Momo!
You found him in the middle of the ocean? A complete miracle, I say...
Well, we heard a voice while under the surface...
"Luffy! What great fortune! Youreally are alive!
You... fell off too?
Aye, we fled from Kaido by way of Shinobu's kite.
But, Luffy..!
To allow our egress, Kiku and Kin'emon gave their lives... Before our very eyes...!
Save it for later! Yer always like this!
You're the General! This ain't over yet!
Stop whining!
Ain't nothin' over 'til Kaido's ass is kicked!
Luffytaro! You mustn't be so harsh!
1/11
I told ya to stop sobbing, Momo!
You're the future Shogun, ain't ya?!
Attaboy.
I want more! Meat!
We get it already! We're gonna go hunt some down!
Meat!
You're getting weaker, aren't ya, Straw Hat..?
U If you die now, I'm gonna be in deep crap!
If you don't beat him, there's no way I'm getting out of the country!
You gotta hang in there!
Momo!
HAT W/
W/
Take me back up there!
Turn into a dragon and fly me there!
Eh?!
111 11//1 Awhuh?!
I'm takin'...
...Kaido down!
TO BE CONTINDED